Re-Torque optimization
In this video, you will learn about the optimization content related to the Re-Torque function.
Smart Torque
Smart Torque tools will help you quickly draw a torque line based on the segment level set on each line.
Select the Smart Torque tool in the 2D window.
Smart Torque dialogue frame will be displayed, you can adjust the number of segments.
After adjusting the number of segments, you can click and drag the mouse on the 2D panel to create a Smart Torque line.
Click again to complete the creation of the Smart Torque line and this line will be divided according to the number of segments.
When the area formed by the Torque line is closed, the internal line will appear.
When you click on a smart Torque line border that has been created, you can adjust its number of segments again.
You can add a number of segments, and if the 3D
intelligence of the Smart Torque line is relevant, you can use the Numbers tool to adjust additions and adjustments.
You can use the Therefore tool reduced the number of segments.
After all areas are closed, click on the Create button in the smart top dialogue box to create a top face based on the smart top line.
You can also create a smart top line with the top face that has been created.
Select the clear option in the smart top dialogue box to delete all the created smart top lines, but it will not affect the top face that has been created.
And the newly created area can be created by creating a tool as the top face.
The internal smart top line will only appear in the smart top area, forming a triangle or square shape.
Click on the Create button to create a smart top line.
You can also add a smart top line.
When the top point is created on the outside of the board with the sewing line, you can see the support top point automatically generated on the other side of the sewing line.
These support top points will help you to absorb and create the top structure corresponding to the top point on the other side of the sewing line.
Now you can easily insert the support in the嘛 one of the upper edge of the board, bring the top point to the top of the board and insert it in the center of the board from the bottom.
Now you can easily insert the support in the side of the board.
Insert the support in the side of the board on the top of the board.
As I said before, the support for support can be usually separate, so I use this tool to adjust it for that.
By following this step, you can easily insert the support in the bottom of the board.